

IVAN VILDE











ABOUT ME

I'm 26 years old front-end developer. I had an experience of creating single-page application using JS library, frameworks. Converting design to landing page.
Interested in creating GUIs and related logic.
I'm fond of sports, especially boxing, skiing.
In my work, first of all, I am interested in well-established processes, the possibility of development and

SKILLS

- JAVASCRIPT
- TYPESCRIPT
- REACT.JS / NEXT.JS
- REDUX / REDUX-TOOLKIT
- THUNK / SAGA
- VUE.JS / VUEX
- DOCKER
- PRETTIER / ESLINT
- WEBSOCKET
- MATERIAL UI / BOOTSTRAP
- REST API / AXIOS
- UNIT TESTS / STORYBOOK
- HTML / PUG
- SCSS / SASS / STYL
- GIT / GITHUB / GITLAB

CONTACT DETAILS

Mobile Phone:

+79296372677

Email Address:

dev.vilde@gmail.com

City: Moscow

LANGUAGE

English intermediate in progress

WORK EXPERIENCE

LLC "FUTURE"

implementation.

Front-end develope | 2021 December - Now

Task decomposition, execution time estimation, time tracking in bitrix

Development of components on React / Next for date, time, site search, creation of forms

Component Development with Vue

Development of a one-page site on pug

Working with typescript, eslint, redux, vuex, docker, git, gitlab, webpack, styl, sass

Interaction with backend, designer

LLC "TRANSCONVERTER"

Technical Service Engineer | 2019 - May 2020

Diagnostics, computer diagnostics and repair of Siemens high-voltage converters. Work with Siemens software.

LLC "ARSENAL-CLIMATE"

Technical Service Engineer | 2018 - April 2019

Service and repair of refrigeration and compressor equipment. Software setting of air conditioning equipment.

EDUCATIONS

IT-INCUBATOR.BY

Front-end developer. React, Redux, TypeScript | 2020 - 2021